

#### **About**

Innovative, task-driven professional with 1+ years of experience in web design and development across diverse industries. Equipped with a record of success in consistently identifying and providing the technological needs of companies through ingenious innovation.

#### Contact



+91 7016831173



hexorbusa@gmail.com



Rajkot, Gujarat, India, 360004

### **Education**

Shri S'ad Vidya Mandal Institute of Technology (GTU) Bachelor of Engineering (BE-IT) 8.67 CGPA 2017-2021

DR. R.D.Gardi Education Campus (G.S.E.B) 12th(HSC) 71.40 percentage 2015-2017

Saraswati vidhyamandir (G.S.E.B) 10th(ssc) 83.33 percentage 2014-2015

#### Area of interest

- · Small & Large Scale System Development
- · Project Management And Leading
- · Sales And Marketing

# **VIVEK BUSA**

# **MERN Stack Developer**

**Professional Skills** 

	~	
HTML/CSS /BS		Sublime Text
Javascript		Vscode
Reactjs & Redux		Git
Nodejs		Postman
PHP		Firebase
Mongodb		
Mysql		

**Tools** 

# **Experience**

# Full stack developer(Full time)

#### Craftbox Technology, Rajkot June 2021-Present

- Here I was doing some basic task of Node JS, React JS and Mongodb.
- Project manager and Developer of 3 Full dynamic live E-Commerce website based on core PHP
  - · Wecard wecard.in
    - This is an e-commerce website of digital business card in which you can design your own card.
  - Sattvavibes sattvavibes.com
    - This is an e-commerce website of digital musical products here we can purchase music track and download those tracks to relax our mind and soul.
    - Main functionality of this website is that when its open in any country the price changes automatically according to country's currency.
  - Markon Life Care markonlifecare.com
    - This is a simple corporate website for surgical lifecare products

#### Front-end Web Developer(Intern)

# Skill Safari , Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Aug 2020-Nov 2020

- Learn basic to intermediate level HTML5,CSS3 and modern javascript
- Developed user interface web pages with modern javascript,HTML5 and
- Did some small and basic task like making some static landing pages and some logical javascript task.

# Project for learning purpose

#### **Chatting App**

- This is a basic chatting app develop on React JS, Node JS.
- It use Socket.io library for a real time data transfer.Learn basic to intermediate level HTML5,CSS3 and modern javascript

# Weather App

• This is a simple weather app which is used for real time API data.